Jacob Petersen

951-227-6991 jcb.petersen1995@gmail.com 10506 Hyacinth Pl, Highlands Ranch, CO 80129

Profile

Customer-service focused professional with experience in both the sales and service departments at luxury automotive dealerships. Maintains excellent relationships with guests and generates returned business. Searching for my next opportunity to grow in a high-line automotive environment.

Experience

AUTOMOTIVE SERVICE ADVISOR, MERCEDES-BENZ; LITTLETON, CO – JUNE 2018 - PRESENT AUTOMOTIVE SERVICE ADVISOR, MERCEDES-BENZ; ESCONDIDO, CA – FEBRUARY 2017- JUNE 2018

As a Service Advisor I'm responsible for promoting automotive services and repairs by identifying the need for and selling service work while maintaining a high degree of client satisfaction. I'm a representative of the Mercedes-Benz brand and implement all process and procedures in order to provide the best for our clients.

SHIFT LEADER, STARBUCKS COFFEE COMPANY; NORCO, CA - 2013-2017

As a Starbucks Shift Supervisor, I assisted the store manager in executing store operations during scheduled shifts. I deployed partners and delegate tasks to create the Starbucks Experience for our customers by providing legendary customer service with prompt service, quality beverages and products, and maintaining a clean and comfortable store environment. I was responsible for modeling and acting in accordance with Starbucks guiding principles.

Education

Centennial High School, Corona, CA – High School Diploma - 2013

University of Denver, Denver, CO - Full Stack Web Development Program - 2019 - Present

Skills

- experienced customer service partner
- excellent communication verbally, over the phone, and through memos
- decision making skills that benefit both the company and the guests
- vibrant personality with professional demeanor
- resolves on -the-job problems effectively
- meets deadlines and handles multiple assignments at once
- maintains high customer satisfaction ratings

References

Jason Cestaro, General Manager - Mercedes-Benz of Escondido - 310-877-4201

Amber Martin, Store Manager - Starbucks Coffee Company - 909-560-0762

Jerome Seubert, Service Manager - Mercedes-Benz of Littleton - 303-900-4768